# **ERIK CRIBLEY**

Lakewood, OH 44107 | Phone: 330-550-2181 | email: erikcribley@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/erikcribley | Github: https://github.com/erikcribley

Portfolio: https://erikcribley.github.io/Portfolio/

#### **SUMMARY**

Erik is a Full Stack Web Developer with ten years of professional experience in inventory and stocking. He specializes in logging and tracking product, data entry, and communicating between sales associates and warehouse staff. Erik's strengths are: creativity, problem solving, and open-mindedness.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, MongoDB, Node, Express, React

## **EDUCATION**

**Bootcamp Certificate:** Case Western Reserve University, Cleveland, OH - 10/2019 **BA in Film Production:** Bowling Green State University, Bowling Green, OH

## **PROJECTS**

**NYTimes: Fiction This!** 

https://github.com/erikcribley/Blue-Team-Project-One.git https://erikcribley.github.io/Blue-Team-Project-One

- this application dynamically updates the New York Times Best Seller List
- I developed the application using API routes, Ajax jQuery, and JavaScript

## **Dungeon Crawler**

https://github.com/NT5K/Dungeon\_Crawl https://dungeon-crawl.herokuapp.com

- a fantasy-themed, choose-your-own-adventure style game
- uses JavaScript, SQL, Express, Node

#### **PowerUp**

https://github.com/erikcribley/Project3

# https://powerup5000.herokuapp.com/

- a sci-fi themed gamified productivity app
- Uses JavaScript, React, SQL, Express, Node

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**WAREHOUSE ASSOCIATE, APPLIED MSS (STRONGSVILLE, OH)** 08/2017 – CURRENT Relocates merchandise from bulk area to prime picking locations.

**SHIPPING ASSOCIATE, RIDDELL (NORTH RIDGEVILLE, OH)** 09/2016 – 08/2017 Packed and staged product for shipping.

**INVENTORY MANAGEMENT, LKQ (MAPLE HEIGHTS, OH)** 05/2013 - 03/2016

Processed incoming stock into inventory management system.

# **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

**Thru-hiked 2,189 mile Appalachian Trail** 03/2016 - 09/2016